diggygames.com 2013-05-17

# Free Games - Play Flash Games Online at Diggy Games

## privacy policy

DiggyGames.com is committed to protecting your privacy online. To further this commitment, we have adopted an Online Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store, and use the information collected about you online. What information does DiggyGames.com collect? DiggyGames may request and/or collect information from you on a voluntary basis when you: register with us, or when you send questions or comments via e-mail to DiggyGames.com customer support. The requested information may include personal information such as your name and e-mail address. If you are under the age of 13, you will need your parent or guardian's consent before you can provide any personal information to us for purposes of registration and other online activities. E-mail By allowing you to send e-mail to us, we are not attempting to collect any personal information about you. We will only use personal information (such as name and e-mail address) contained in your e-mail to respond to your specific inquiry or comments in the e-mail. Although we may retain your e-mail for a period of time, we will not use any personal information contained in your e-mail for any purpose other than responding to your specific inquiry or comments. Whatever the activity may be, we will only collect information to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to fulfill your requests and our legitimate business objectives. Cookies DiggyGames.com may use cookies to improve the use of our websites. A 'cookie' is a small file that websites often store on a user's computer. Storage of cookies on your system provides an easy and convenient method for us to personalize your experience on our websites. For example, cookies allow us to remember your screen name, tell us that you have visited our website before, and may contain information that will make your next visit to our website more enjoyable. However, we do not use cookies to store personal information such as your name. In addition, DiggyGames.com does not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. You can always disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer. IP Addresses DiggyGames.com may also collect your IP address for safety and security purposes. An IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet. Log Files Other non-personal information collected by DiggyGames.comis in the form of logs - files that record website activity, including how many 'hits' a particular web page is getting (a.k.a., 'click-through data'). For example, log file entries are generated every time a visitor clicks the 'Home' icon on our site. These entries enable DiggyGames.comto assess overall site activity, track interest in advertised sales, track interest in purchase behavior, and troubleshoot technical concerns. Through the use of log files, we may also collect certain demographic information such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows 98 or Mac OS), and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink). Linking to third party sites To provide relevant information not found on our Web site, DiggyGames.com may provide links from our Web sites to third party Web sites and we encourage our users to read third party sites' privacy policies before submitting personal information. All the downloads and Exe files provided on this site are from a 3rd party and DiggyGames.com is not responsible for any files or adware that gets installed by their games and screensavers. They contain several adware products so download and install @ your own risk. DiggyGames.com resumes NO responsibility. DiggyGames.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of the content of third party sites'. DiggyGames.com hereby disclaims any representations or warranties expressed on any site other than its own site. Who is collecting my personal information? Any personal information that you disclose while visiting any of our websites is collected by DiggyGames.com, and is used in the manner specified above. Questions and Complaints If you have any questions, complaints or comments regarding our Privacy Policy Statement, please contact us @ admin (AT) DiggyGames.com By using this site, you signify your assent to the DiggyGames.com Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this site. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Please check back from time to time to ensure that you are aware of these changes. Your continued use of this site will signify your acceptance of these changes. 

Insert Your  
Advertisement Here
